[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor delivered the line All right. I\u2019ll respect your traditions. Ill go to the headmaster and Ill lie!?", "correct_answer": "Brendon Frasier in School Ties", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Damon in School Ties", "Andrew McCarthy in Class", "Rob Lowe in Oxford Blues"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is interesting to note that contrary to popular belief, by scientific definiton, there were no dinosaurs of this type.", "correct_answer": "neither flying nor marine dinosaurs", "incorrect_answers": ["flying dinosaurs", "cold-blooded dinosaurs", "marine dinosaurs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times does Heath Ledger ask the question, Did I ever tell you how I got these scars? in The Dark Knight?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "5", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the movie Cocktail premiere?", "correct_answer": "1988", "incorrect_answers": ["1986", "1987", "1989"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common length of a full grown male Komodo Dragon?", "correct_answer": "9 feet", "incorrect_answers": ["11 feet", "8 feet", "6 feet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US state had the most estimated farmland for 2000?", "correct_answer": "Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["South Dakota", "Kansas", "Montana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can you name the singer who had a big music hit with Mr. Bojangles.", "correct_answer": "Ronald Clyde Crosby", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these  answers", "Tom Waites", "Willie Nelson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People with anxiety usually know they have anxiety.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which set contains only  prime numbers?", "correct_answer": "2, 3, 5, 7,11,13, 17", "incorrect_answers": ["1, 4, 11, 13, 15, 17", "2, 3, 5, 7, 9, 11, 37", "1, 3, 5, 7, 9, 11, 13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Water sticks to itself. What is this property called?", "correct_answer": "Molecular cohesion", "incorrect_answers": ["Delaification", "Atomic pedalation", "Hydrogenation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Jafars parrot in the Disney movie Aladdin?", "correct_answer": "Iago", "incorrect_answers": ["Abu", "Birdbrain", "Pauly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 1978 thriller in which a Nazi death-camp doctor attempts to clone Adolf Hitler.", "correct_answer": "The Boys from Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Heaven Can Wait", "Foul Play", "Every Which Way But Loose"]}]